Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
You're only coming back now?
هل ستعود الآن فقط؟
How's your injury?
كيف حال إصابتك؟
You've certainly nailed that part
لقد أتقنت هذا الجزء بالتأكيد
at the festival.
في المهرجان.
You were just stalling with me,
لقد كنت تماطل معي فقط،
playing along,
اللعب على طول،
then had those people come after me,
ثم جاء هؤلاء الناس بعدي،
didn't you?
ألم تفعل؟
I don't know those people.
انا لا اعرف هؤلاء الناس.
Are you still trying to lie to me?
هل لازلت تحاول الكذب علي؟
I saw with my own eyes that you gave the order.
لقد رأيت بعيني أنك أعطيت الأمر.
Those assassins were protecting you
هؤلاء القتلة كانوا يحمونك
but closing in on me at every step.
لكنهم يقتربون مني في كل خطوة.
Then why would you be dumb enough to save me?
إذن لماذا تكون غبيًا بما يكفي لإنقاذي؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I was stupid.
لقد كنت غبيًا.
Because I was afraid I was wrong,
لأنني كنت خائفة من أن أكون مخطئة،
and those people would really hurt you.
وهؤلاء الأشخاص سوف يؤذونك حقًا.
Young Marshal Huo, Governor wants to see you.
المارشال الشاب هوو، الحاكم يريد رؤيتك.
When Young Marshal Huo was unconscious,
عندما كان المارشال الشاب هيو فاقدًا للوعي،
he gave me this nine-linked ring
لقد أعطاني هذا الخاتم ذو التسعة حلقات
and told me to redeem the prize.
وطلب مني استرداد الجائزة.
He said it was for you.
قال أنها لك.
I've never seen him care about anyone like this.
لم أرى أبدًا أنه يهتم بأحد مثل هذا.
I'm only his sister.
أنا أخته فقط.
=Episode 9=
=الحلقة 9=
Did anything unusual happen
هل حدث أي شيء غير عادي؟
at the festival?
في المهرجان؟
(Xiu,)
(شيو)
(your ears are red.)
(أذنيك حمراء.)
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
Did you hear me?
هل سمعتني؟
Was there anything strange?
هل كان هناك أي شيء غريب؟
There was nothing unusual.
لم يكن هناك شيئا غير عادي.
Don't forget
لا تنسى
why I took you in in the first place.
لماذا أخذتك في المقام الأول.
♪In a gentle night♪
♪في ليلة لطيفة♪
♪A bare face awaiting blush♪
♪وجه عارٍ ينتظر الاحمرار♪
♪Cups clink, voices overlap♪
♪أكواب تتصادم، أصوات متداخلة♪
♪We switch our roles♪
♪نحن نبدل الأدوار♪
♪Darkness fades, and daylight breaks♪
♪يتلاشى الظلام، ويشرق ضوء النهار♪
♪Evening winds usher in the night♪
♪رياح المساء تبشر بقدوم الليل♪
♪On the brink of the world's collapse♪
♪على حافة انهيار العالم♪
♪We dance the dance of death♪
♪نحن نرقص رقصة الموت♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪
How could he be so ruthless?
كيف يمكن أن يكون قاسياً إلى هذه الدرجة؟
You're his son by blood.
أنت ابنه بالدم.
I'm just the watchdog he raised.
أنا مجرد كلب الحراسة الذي رباه.
Don't look at me like that.
لا تنظر إلي بهذه الطريقة.
Don't make me think you mean more than you say.
لا تجعلني أعتقد أنك تقصد أكثر مما تقول.
Cheng
تشنغ
told me everything.
أخبرني بكل شيء.
♪See, all that is fearless♪
♪انظر، كل هذا لا يعرف الخوف♪
♪The love without answer♪
♪الحب بلا جواب♪
♪The hate without form♪
♪الكراهية بلا شكل♪
Thank you for the gift.
شكرا على الهدية.
I really like it.
أنا حقا أحب ذلك.
♪Concealed beneath, the deepest despair and burning desire♪
♪مخفية تحتها أعمق اليأس والرغبة الملتهبة♪
I honestly can't tell
أنا بصراحة لا أستطيع أن أقول
if you're being sincere or…
إذا كنت صادقا أو...
Does it matter?
هل يهم؟
♪In a gentle night♪
♪في ليلة لطيفة♪
♪A bare face awaiting blush♪
♪وجه عارٍ ينتظر الاحمرار♪
♪Cups clink, voices overlap♪
♪أكواب تتصادم، أصوات متداخلة♪
♪We switch our roles♪
♪نحن نبدل الأدوار♪
I'm not a good person.
أنا لست شخصا جيدا.
I'm prepared to cross over if I have to.
أنا مستعد للعبور إذا كان علي ذلك.
♪Evening winds usher in the night♪
♪رياح المساء تبشر بقدوم الليل♪
So?
لذا؟
So…
لذا…
I want you to stay.
أريد منك أن تبقى.
Don't leave me behind again, please?
لا تتركني خلفك مرة أخرى من فضلك؟
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪
Are you still sleeping?
هل مازلت نائما؟
I should go.
ينبغي لي أن أذهب.
Did you know all along she was Huo Qingwan?
هل كنت تعلم منذ البداية أنها هيو تشينغوان؟
You said you were her fan
قلت أنك من معجبيها
and even asked me to invite her to my aunt's birthday banquet.
وحتى أنها طلبت مني أن أدعوها إلى حفل عيد ميلاد خالتي.
I thought
اعتقدت
you were just helping me
لقد كنت تساعدني فقط
win my aunt's favor.
الفوز بمصلحة عمتي.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
You found
لقد وجدت
Madam Huo's real daughter.
ابنة السيدة هيو الحقيقية.
Doesn't this put you
ألا يضعك هذا؟
in a better position within the Huo family?
في وضع أفضل داخل عائلة هوو؟
A better position?
وضع أفضل؟
I've lived as an outsider in the Huo family for all these years.
لقد عشت كغريب في عائلة هوو طوال هذه السنوات.
I thought my struggles were finally over.
اعتقدت أن صراعاتي قد انتهت أخيرا.
But you had me send Huo Qingwan back with my own hands.
لكنك جعلتني أرسل هوو تشينغوان بيدي.
Don't be upset.
لا تنزعج.
Huo Qingwan returning
عودة هيو تشينغوان
to the Huo family
إلى عائلة هوو
benefits all of us.
إنها مفيدة لنا جميعا.
It only benefits the Sheng family, doesn't it?
إنه يصب في مصلحة عائلة شينغ فقط، أليس كذلك؟
I've done so much for you
لقد فعلت الكثير من أجلك
all these years.
كل هذه السنوات.
You're not allowed to love anyone else.
ليس مسموح لك أن تحب أي شخص آخر.
You must marry me
يجب عليك الزواج مني
and make me the young madam of the Sheng family.
واجعلني السيدة الشابة لعائلة شنغ.
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪